<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lima y Sal</title>
    <description>Stories and pictures about food, life, adventures, food, drinks and food in Lima, Peru.
</description>
    <link>http://bchartoff.github.io/lima-y-sal/lima-y-sal/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://bchartoff.github.io/lima-y-sal/lima-y-sal/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 10:06:21 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 10:06:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nuestra casa es su casa</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re in Lima!!! This blog will be a place to share stories about our life and adventures here in Peru. So, watch this space for effusive descriptions of ceviche, fruit, hole in the wall restaurants, swanky restaurants, markets, and theoretically things that aren’t food (from time to time).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a first post, we want to give you a tour of our home. We live in Miraflores, a beautiful neighborhood in downtown Lima. When you walk in, you see our living room/dining room. How stylish is this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/lima-y-sal/assets/img/nuestra_casa/living_room.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;great couch right?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re also thrilled to finally have an apartment with an open kitchen! It’s small but mighty. No oven, but we’re going to see if we can make a combination of appliances work: a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnet.com/products/ninja-cooking-system/&quot;&gt;fancy multi-use crock pot&lt;/a&gt;, a grill, and a toaster oven. And it’s open to the living room! Planning on many, many dinner parties here, and I won’t be holed up in the kitchen. Hooray!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/lima-y-sal/assets/img/nuestra_casa/kitchen.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;This is where the magic happens&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The living room also has this balcony! We’re planning on planting some herbs in this planter. Shaping up to be a dream apartment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/lima-y-sal/assets/img/nuestra_casa/balcony.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Sometimes there are hummingbirds out here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our bedroom is also lovely. Our landlord has pretty great taste.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/lima-y-sal/assets/img/nuestra_casa/bedroom.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Cozy Lima winter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And there’s a second bedroom! This is where you’ll be staying when you come visit. Stylish, roomy, a great home base for you Lima adventures. Come visit, seriously, look how great this bedroom is. It’s also my office, and Natalie’s clothes room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/lima-y-sal/assets/img/nuestra_casa/guest.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;That bed’s as comfortable as it looks. Come visit for serious.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the bathroom is pretty cool too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/lima-y-sal/assets/img/nuestra_casa/bano.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Love those tiles on the wall&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lots more posts coming soon, can’t wait to share our stories and memories with you!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 16:59:40 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://bchartoff.github.io/lima-y-sal/lima-y-sal/posts/2016/05/30/nuestra-casa.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://bchartoff.github.io/lima-y-sal/lima-y-sal/posts/2016/05/30/nuestra-casa.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>posts</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
